woundedwarriorproject.org 2019-02-22

# Effective as of February 20, 2019

                                                                     Effective as of February 20, 2019
                                             Privacy Policies
This document describes Wounded Warrior Project’s (“WWP”) use of information regarding the warriors
and families we serve, financial supporters of our mission, supporters under the age of 18, and general
visitors to our website.
                                      General User Privacy Policy
This privacy policy applies to general users of the WWP website and describes how WWP protects
information you provide when you use this website.
Although elements of this policy may apply to the veterans we serve, their caregivers, and our donors
who visit our website, we do collect additional data from these groups of people. Warriors and their
caregivers who register for WWP’s programs and services can find additional information about how
WWP uses their information on our Alumni and Caregiver Privacy Policy. Donors and supporters of
WWP can find additional information about how WWP uses their information on our Donor Privacy
Policy. Both policies may be found below.
WWP is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. It is our goal that you fully understand
how we collect information, how we use that information, and the steps we’ve taken to protect that
information. We will update this policy from time to time, so make sure to check this page periodically.
If you have any questions about this policy, please email us at wwplegal@woundedwarriorproject.org.
What type of information does WWP collect?
There are two basic types of information that WWP might collect: personal and non-personal information.
As you browse the WWP website, you may opt to provide WWP with personal information. Personal
information is information that contains identifiers such as your name, address, phone number, or email
address.
WWP may also collect non-personal information from you such as an internet protocol address (typically
referred to as an “IP address” and defined below) and browsing variables (like your web browser, referral
links, or how much time you spent at our website). Although this information may on rare occasion be
used to identify you, WWP typically uses this information to improve your experience and the experience
of other visitors to our website. WWP may use cookies to collect this type of information.
What’s a cookie? A cookie is a small data text file that individual websites store on your computer’s
hard drive – if your web browser permits. The website can later retrieve that cookie to let us know
you’ve been to our site before. Cookies typically make your use of the site easier, make the site run more
smoothly, and help us to maintain a secure site. Many websites use cookies. You are free to decline our
cookies if your browser permits, but some parts of our site may not work properly if you do that.
What’s an IP address? An IP address is a unique number, assigned to each and every computer and
other device on the Internet. Your computer, your phone, your e-reader, and other electronic devices, are
all assigned IP addresses.
When does WWP collect this information?
We collect non-personal information from you as you use any of the pages on our website. We collect
personal information from you only when you specifically provide it to us – for example, if you fill out a
form or send us an email.
How does WWP use the information we collect?
WWP uses information from different site visitors in different ways. We generally use information
provided to us through the donation process in accordance with the Donor Privacy Policy; we generally use

                                                                        Effective as of February 20, 2019
information provided to us by the warriors and caregivers we serve in accordance with the Alumni and
Caregiver Privacy Policy. Both policies may be found below.
On rare occasion, we use personal information provided by general users of our website who are not
warriors or caregivers and are not engaging in the donation process. We might, for example, ask for your
information if you contact a local WWP representative or if you upload a personal video message to our
warriors.
We may also use your personal and non-personal information in the following ways:
     -    Entering your information into our databases for internal record keeping, reporting, and data
          analysis;
     -    Communicating with you to obtain your input, provide information about our programs and events,
          or request contributions (provided you have opted to receive such communications);
     -    Improving our programs and services;
     -    Customizing our website according to your interests;
     -    Sharing information with third parties who help us manage our website and databases, and who
          assist us with our marketing efforts; and
     -    Sharing information with third parties as required by law, or a part of a legal process;
We have contracted with Yahoo, and other online marketing companies, to monitor certain pages of our
website for the purpose of reporting web traffic, statistics, advertisement “click-throughs,” and other
activities on our website. No personally identifiable data is transferred to Yahoo by us. Where
authorized by us, Yahoo may use cookies and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous
statistics about our website visitors.
If you choose, you may opt out from Yahoo’s collection of such information outside of the Yahoo
distribution network by clicking on the following link:
http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/opt_out/targeting/details.html.
You may learn more about your control over this information by clicking here:
http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
We also reserve the right to use non-personal information, such as an IP address, to identify a user when
we believe it is necessary to protect the compelling interests of our websites, the warriors we serve, their
caregivers, our donors, our employees, or others, or to comply with laws, court orders, or law
enforcement requests.
Does WWP share my information?
WWP may share your personal and non-personal information as discussed herein. We do not, however,
sell or rent the personal information of our general website users for profit.
Does WWP track my online activity while I’m not on the WWP site?
Cookies and other technology may be used to track non-personal information about your web-browsing
habits. For example, if a significant portion of our visitors all browse to the same website immediately
after visiting us, we may use this information to improve your experience at our site.
WWP respects web browser “do not track” signals and other mechanisms that provide you the ability to
opt out of having your personal information or online activities collected. But remember, unless you have
selected the “do not track” function in your web browser, third parties (not just WWP) may collect
personal information about your online activities over time and across different websites.
How does WWP secure my personal information?
WWP is committed to ensuring that your personal information is secure. Your trust in us is important, so
we have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the

                                                                        Effective as of February 20, 2019
information we collect. Records containing personal information are stored at secure facilities; our
websites use SSL (a tool used to verify the legitimacy of a website); and our employees are provided
training on how to treat your data securely.
Will you contact me if I give WWP my information?
If you provide us with your contact information, we may provide you with information about how you
can help this generation of injured veterans. However, if you would not like to receive these messages,
you can opt out of having your personal information used for certain purposes when we ask for your
contact information.
If you are already receiving those messages and would like to stop receiving them, you may opt out by
following the instructions included in the message or by calling our Donor Care team at
877.TEAM.WWP (832.6997).
If you would like to immediately opt out of all communications, please complete this form, and select
“Remove from Mailing/Email Lists”: https://support.woundedwarriorproject.org/Default.aspx?tsid=459
Links to other websites and third party services
Sometimes we’ll provide you with a link to another website or service. We typically do this in order to
provide you additional information about one of our sponsors to others who support the mission of WWP.
WWP may also include other electronic services on our website. For example, this could include a tool
that allows you to contact your local politicians, or to create a custom message to send to veterans. These
services are typically provided by third parties, and may require you to agree to that service provider’s
own privacy statement and terms of use. This policy does not cover these third party services or how
those third parties may use the information you provide them. We encourage you to review those privacy
policies and terms of use.
How do I update my information?
Please contact the WWP Donor Care team using this form:
https://support.woundedwarriorproject.org/Default.aspx?tsid=459
Do you collect information about minors?
Yes; in limited circumstances WWP collects information from general users under the age of 18. Please
see our Minor Privacy Policy below.
What if I have questions about this policy?
We’d love to hear from you. Please email us at wwplegal@woundedwarriorproject.org with any
questions about this policy. You can also snail-mail us a letter at Wounded Warrior Project, Attention:
Legal, 4899 Belfort Road, Suite 300, Jacksonville, Florida 32256.
                                  Alumni and Caregiver Privacy Policy
This Alumni and Caregiver Privacy Policy applies to warriors and their caregivers who register with
WWP to receive the benefits of Wounded Warrior Project’s programs and services. If you register for our
programs and services, rest assured that we use industry-standard safeguards to protect your data,
including firewalls, physical safeguards, and encryption.
This policy describes how Wounded Warrior Project protects information which warriors and their
caregivers provide in conjunction with their registration with WWP, and applies regardless of whether the

                                                                         Effective as of February 20, 2019
registration occurred online, over the phone, or in person. Throughout this privacy policy, or the
“policy,” warriors and their caregivers who register for WWP’s programs and services may be referred to
as “Alumni,” “Caregivers,” or simply, “you.”
This policy may supplement the General User Privacy Policy (above), which covers all users of the WWP
website. Although this policy is intended to compliment that General User Privacy Policy, this policy
applies specifically to information you provide us in conjunction with your registration or your status as
an Alumni or Caregiver. This policy also supplements the Donor Privacy Policy (below), which applies
to any information you provide in conjunction a donation to WWP. For example: if you navigate to a
donation page on our website and make a contribution to WWP, the information you provide during your
donation will be stored in accordance with the Donor Privacy Policy. If you navigate to the registration
page and register as an Alumni, that data will be used in accordance with this policy. If you provide us
additional information relating to your participation in our programs and services, that information will
also be governed by this policy.
It is our goal that you fully understand how we collect information, how we use that information, and the
steps we’ve taken to protect that information. We will update this policy from time to time, so make sure
to check this page periodically. If you have any questions about this policy, please email us at
wwplegal@woundedwarriorproject.org.
What type of information does WWP collect?
WWP collects different information depending on whether you’re an Alumni or Family Support member.
Alumni: As an Alumni, we will ask you for your service information, such as your branch, rank, and
service dates. We will also ask for your contact information, such as name, email address, telephone
number, and mailing address.
We will also ask other identifying information, such as date of birth, gender, and type and location of
your injury. Lastly, we’ll ask you for eligibility documentation. This may include a DD214, VA ratings
decision, enlisted record brief or officer record brief, medical evaluation board or physical evaluation
board, current unit orders to a warrior transition unit or battalion, line of duty documentation, or Purple
Heart orders or citation.
Once you are registered as an Alumni, depending on your level of involvement with our services, we may
ask you for additional information. This may include questions about your individual hobbies and
interests, benefits claims details, basic financial information, basic physical and mental fitness details, and
other information that may be relevant to the particular program or service you are interested in.
Family Support: When you register as a Family Support member, you will be asked for your relationship
status with an eligible warrior; i.e., whether you are related to a veteran who served in the military on or
after September 11, 2001. We’ll ask for information about the warrior you support, including his or her
name, service details such as branch, rank, and service dates.
We will also ask you for your contact information, such as name, email address, telephone number, and
mailing address, as well as other identifying information like date of birth and gender.
Lastly, we will ask you for eligibility documentation of the warrior you support. This may include a
DD214, VA ratings decision, enlisted record brief or officer record brief, medical evaluation board or
physical evaluation board, current unit orders to a warrior transition unit or battalion, line of duty
documentation, or Purple Heart orders or citation.
Once you are registered as a Family Support member, depending on your level of involvement with our
services, we may ask you for additional information. This may include questions about your individual
hobbies and interests, benefits claims details, basic financial information, basic physical and mental
fitness details, and other information that may be relevant to the particular program or service you are
interested in.

                                                                       Effective as of February 20, 2019
Whether you attempt to register as an Alumni or Family Support member, in certain circumstances WWP
may gather information about you from publicly-available resources.
When does WWP collect this information?
We collect your contact information and service details when you register for WWP’s programs and
services. This can be done online through our website, in person with a WWP employee, or over the
phone. We may collect the additional information mentioned above through conversations with you.
Though you are not required to provide this information, your ability to participate in a particular program
or service may be impacted if we don’t have relevant information. For example, if you are interested in
participating in one of our Physical Health and Wellness initiatives, we may ask you for your current
fitness levels and fitness goals. If you participate in our Benefits Service program, we may ask for your
prior benefits claims documents and other related information.
We may also be provided information about you from other groups who refer you to us to take advantage
of our programs and services. They will typically notify you and seek your consent before providing us
with such information. No matter how we receive your information, rest assured we will use it in
accordance with this policy.
How does WWP use the information we collect?
Generally, WWP uses this information to tailor our programs and services to fit your needs.
We will use your contact information and other information that we collect for the following reasons:
     -   For internal record keeping, reporting, and data analysis;
     -   To communicate with you to obtain your input and provide information about our programs and
         services;
     -   To improve our programs and services;
     -   To customize our website according to your interests;
     -   To share information with third parties who help us deliver our programs and services;
     -   To share information with third parties who deliver their own programs and services to veterans
         and their caregivers;
     -   As required by law, or as part of a legal process.
We will use your eligibility documentation to ensure whether you are eligible to receive WWP’s program
services. Once WWP has verified your eligibility, it is WWP’s policy to remove these documents from our
systems.
How does WWP share my information?
WWP shares your personal and non-personal information only as discussed above. We will not share
your information with a third party that does not provide services (or help us provide services) to our
Alumni and Family Support members, nor for purposes of adding you to a mailing list.
We will never sell or rent your personal information for profit.
This Policy does not apply to any information that you provide to these third parties, and we encourage
you to ask those third parties any questions you may have about their use of your data.
How does WWP secure my personal information?
We have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the
information we collect. Records containing personal information are stored at secure facilities; our
websites use SSL (a tool used to verify the legitimacy of a website); and we train our employees on how
to treat your data securely. Additionally, when WWP shares your information with third parties, WWP
takes reasonable steps to ensure that third party has sufficient safeguards in place to protect your

                                                                      Effective as of February 20, 2019
information.
Will you use my information to contact me?
Yes. From time to time, a WWP employee will reach out to you to confirm your contact information and
ensure you are taking advantage of our programs and services. We will also send you weekly emails
informing you of programs and services available in your area.
If you would to opt out of receiving emails or phone calls, you may do so by following the instructions
included in the message or by calling our Resource Center at 888.997.2586.
How do I update my information?
Please contact the WWP Resource Center at 888.997.2586
Services provided by third parties
As mentioned above, WWP may provide your information to third parties who assist us in providing
programs and services to you or who provide similar programs and services. As part of their services,
they may ask you for your contact information or other personal information. This Policy does not apply
to information that you provide to these third parties, and we encourage you to ask those third parties any
questions you may have about their use of your data.
Do you collect information about minors?
WWP does not knowingly collect, use, or disclose personal information about Alumni or Caregivers who
are under 18 years of age.
What if I have questions about this FAQ?
We’d be happy to hear from you. Please email us at wwplegal@woundedwarriorproject.org with any
questions about this policy. You can also snail-mail us a letter at Wounded Warrior Project, Attention:
Legal, 4899 Belfort Road, Suite 300, Jacksonville, Florida 32256.
                                           Donor Privacy Policy
This privacy policy applies to WWP supporters and describes how WWP uses information you provide
when you make a donation to us or sign up to receive emails (the “Donation Process”). When you
provide us your information, rest assured that WWP uses industry-standard security measures, including
encryption, firewalls, and physical security to protect your data.
Please remember that this policy applies to information provided by supporters during the Donation
Process. Warriors who register for our programs and services can find more information at the Alumni
and Caregiver Privacy Policy, while users of the website should review the General Privacy Policy. (Both
policies can be found above.) For example, if you register for WWP’s programs and services and also
make a donation to WWP, the information you provide during your registration will be used in
accordance with the Alumni and Caregiver Privacy Policy, while the information you provide while
making your donation will be used in accordance with this policy. Other information may be gathered in
accordance with our General User Privacy Policy.
It is our goal that you fully understand how we collect information, how we use that information, and the
steps we’ve taken to protect that information. We will update this policy from time-to-time, so make sure
to check this page periodically. If you have any questions about this policy, please email us at
wwplegal@woundedwarriorproject.org.

                                                                       Effective as of February 20, 2019
What type of information does WWP collect?
During the Donation Process, WWP will likely ask for information that could be used to identify you.
This includes your contact information, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, and email
address. If you donate via credit or debit card, we will also ask for your card number, expiration date, and
other information necessary to process the transaction. If you donate via check, we may ask for limited
bank information.
When does WWP collect this information?
We collect this information from you during the Donation Process. If you donate online, your donation
will not be processed without certain required information. We may also collect information as we
communicate with you after your donation is made. Third parties may also share your information with
WWP, in accordance with applicable laws, rules, and standards. Rest assured that no matter how we
access your information, we’ll use it only in accordance with this policy.
How does WWP use the information we collect?
We generally use your information to process donations, send you periodic messages, and share with other
parties for the purpose of furthering our mission, as required by law, or as part of a legal process. WWP
may use your information in the following ways:
    -    Enter your information into our databases for internal record keeping, reporting, and data analysis;
    -    Communicate with you to obtain your input, provide you with information, or request contributions
         (provided you have not opted out of receiving such communications);
    -    Provide you with necessary tax information regarding your donation;
    -    Customize our website according to your interests;
    -    Share information with third parties who provide goods and services to WWP (e.g., parties who
         process donations or help us manage our website and databases);
    -    Share information with third parties who may provide services to injured veterans or other groups
         you may be interested in; and
    -    Share information with third parties as required by law, or a part of a legal process.
Does WWP share my information?
WWP may share your personal information as discussed herein. When WWP shares information with
outside organizations, it does so subject to appropriate confidentiality rules designed to protect your
information from unintentional disclosure.
Can I opt out of receiving messages and sharing of my information?
Yes. We provide you with the opportunity to opt out of having your personal information used for certain
purposes when we ask for this information.
If you no longer wish to receive communications from WWP, you may opt out of receiving such
messages by following the instructions included in the message itself. You may also call the Donor
Services team at 877.TEAM.WWP.
If you would like to immediately opt out of all communications, please select “Remove from
Mailing/Email Lists” under the “Inquiry Type” using this form:
https://support.woundedwarriorproject.org/Default.aspx?tsid=459
If you would like to opt out of sharing personal information with other organizations, please select “No
Rent/No Exchange” under the “Inquiry Type” using this form:
https://support.woundedwarriorproject.org/Default.aspx?tsid=459

                                                                     Effective as of February 20, 2019
How does WWP secure my personal information?
WWP strives to ensure the security of your personal information. Your trust in us is important, so we
have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information
we collect. Records containing personal information are stored at secure facilities; our websites use SSL
(a tool used to verify the legitimacy of a website); and we train our employees about how to treat your
data securely.
If you make a donation over the phone or on our website, WWP utilizes industry-standard safeguards to
protect your information including encryption, network firewalls, and physical security. When we work
with other companies to process your payment, those companies also use security measures to protect
your data.
How do I update my information?
Please contact the WWP Donor Care team using this form:
https://support.woundedwarriorproject.org/Default.aspx?tsid=459
Will you contact me if I give WWP my information?
Yes. WWP will send you messages about how we are serving injured veterans and service members and
how you can help. You can opt out of receiving these messages as discussed above in the “Can I opt out
of receiving messages and sharing of my information” section above.
Do you collect information about minors?
Yes; in limited circumstances WWP collects information from supporters who are under the age of 18.
Please see our Minor Privacy Policy below.
What if I have questions about this FAQ?
Please email us at wwplegal@woundedwarriorproject.org with any questions about this policy. You can
also snail-mail us a letter at Wounded Warrior Project, Attention: Legal, 4899 Belfort Road, Suite 300,
Jacksonville, Florida 32256.
                                           Minor Privacy Policy
This privacy policy applies to WWP supporters who are under the age of 18. Note that when you, or
your minor child or guardian, provides us information, WWP will continue to use industry-standard
security measures, including encryption, firewalls, and physical security to protect your data. In short,
WWP applies the same security measures to minor data as we do for our general supporters, but uses the
data for more limited purposes.
WWP collects data about minors wishing to support WWP through specific channels designed to allow
minor participation, such as during registration for WWP’s signature Carry Forward® event or during
registration as a Student Ambassador. Our goal is that you fully understand how we use this
information. We will update this policy from time-to-time, so make sure to check this page periodically.
If you have any questions, email us at wwplegal@woundedwarriorproject.org.
What type of information does WWP collect?
WWP will likely ask for information that could be used to identify you. This includes your contact
information, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, and email address. If you’re registering
for the Carry Forward®, you will also be asked to provide a credit or debit card number, expiration date,

                                                                       Effective as of February 20, 2019
and other information necessary to process the transaction. If you are a minor, you will need your parent
or guardian’s permission to provide their payment information.
When does WWP collect this information?
We collect this information from you during the registration process for Carry Forward® and Student
Ambassadors. We may also collect information as we communicate with you after your registration.
Third parties may also share your information with WWP, in accordance with applicable laws, rules, and
standards. Rest assured that no matter how we access your information, we’ll use it only in accordance
with this policy.
How does WWP use the information we collect?
We generally use your information to process registration, donations, send you periodic messages, and
share with other parties for the purpose of furthering our mission, as required by law, or as part of a legal
process. WWP may use your information in the following ways:
    -    Enter your information into our databases for internal record keeping, reporting, and data analysis;
    -    Communicate with you to obtain your input and provide you with information about your Carry
         Forward® or Student Ambassador registration;
    -    Update you on other events or programs you might be interested in attending or participating in.
    -    Provide you with necessary tax information regarding your donation;
    -    Customize our website according to your interests;
    -    Share information with third parties who provide goods and services to WWP (e.g., parties who
         process donations or help us manage our website and databases);
Does WWP share my information?
WWP may share your personal information as discussed herein. When WWP shares information with
outside organizations, it does so subject to appropriate confidentiality rules designed to protect your
information from unintentional disclosure.
Does WWP use my information for other purposes once I turn 18?
Yes! Once you turn 18, WWP will treat your information in accordance with our Donor Privacy Policy.
(PS, happy birthday!)
Does WWP use information about children under 13 for any specific purposes?
WWP treats information about children under 13 with special care. Children under 13 are not allowed to
register themselves as Student Ambassadors. If you are registering a child under 13 for the Carry
Forward®, WWP strives to ensure that we communicate with that child only to provide communications
about the Carry Forward® event for which he or she is registered. It is WWP policy to delete information
about children under 13 approximately 30 days following the event for which they are registered.
Can I opt out of receiving messages and sharing of my information?
Yes. Please see information above in our Donor Privacy Policy.
How does WWP secure my personal information?
WWP will use the same security methods as discussed above in our Donor Privacy Policy.
How do I update my information?
Please contact the WWP Donor Care team using this form:
https://support.woundedwarriorproject.org/Default.aspx?tsid=459

                                                                    Effective as of February 20, 2019
Will you contact me if I give WWP my information?
Yes. As discussed above, WWP will send you information specifically about the event for which you are
registered, whether you’ve registered as a Student Ambassador or for a Carry Forward® event. You can
opt out of receiving these messages as discussed above in the “Can I opt out of receiving messages and
sharing of my information” section above. It is WWP policy not to directly solicit monetary
contributions from supporters under 18.
What if I have questions about this FAQ?
Please email us at wwplegal@woundedwarriorproject.org with any questions about this policy. You can
also snail-mail us a letter at Wounded Warrior Project, Attention: Legal, 4899 Belfort Road, Suite 300,
Jacksonville, Florida 32256.
